bro broke the car here uncle
wait there
I dropped the Chevrolet to give strength
stopped the car in the middle of the street
and now I stopped mine and stopped traffic
day twenty seven
three days left until the end of the series
tamo together
My My My Music
i told you homeboy
Can't touch this
I'm full of different idea today
to start changing my business
I'm tired of staying
oh it doesn't work out
to motoboys
help my
delivery to us order
3 days left to finish this series
need to run
think outside the box
tamo together
valeu valeu
valeu hand
what a mass I can see
birds raised in cages
believe that flying is a disease
guy believes in you more and you go
it's not working
I will do that now
the Passenger's workshop
will be 1 sustainable brand manja
ha ha ha
no motorcycle
go with bike uncle
another 1 bike in the Center
1 bike in another Russo neighborhood
because there it is distributed
it's good for everyone
i can deliver
fix
not just the day of the person who is my end customer
but also being able to give an option
so someone can make extra income there
a grain
instead of these deliveries
manja has to pass in the cloud
to do a marketing action there
knows face
so i'm unfolding this final line
getting hoarse here
it's going through 1 process you really know
coming here on the skin vei
and the idea
is to generate value
of marketing to be able to sell more of my products
faster and they ask for more
I already have a creative idea for them
and hope it works
man we go on this
ah the result I will put in the Passenger's workshop